designcontest.com 2019-12-21

# DesignContest - Privacy Default

Designcontest LLC (hereinafter, referred to as ‘Company’ or ‘We’ or ‘Our’ or ‘Us’), manages and operates DesignContest.com (hereinafter, referred to as ‘Website’). This Privacy Policy (hereinafter, referred to as ‘Policy’) informs the users (hereinafter, referred to as ‘You’ or ‘Your’) about the manner in which We collect, use, protect, and, disclose their personal and non-personal information. By accessing or using any of the features of this Website, You acknowledge that You have read, understood and agree to the provisions of this Policy. 

### Updates

We reserve the right, in Our sole discretion, to make changes to, and update, this Policy anytime. Any substantial changes or updates to this Policy shall be notified to the registered users of the Website. However, We strongly recommend You to periodically check this page for latest updates to this Policy. 

Last updated on: December 1, 2019

### Your Information — What Collect?

During the course of Your interaction with the Website, We collect some information about you to ensure the smooth functioning of this Website and to provide You with top-notch service quality.

Personal Information: When You fill out the online registration form to join the Website, We collect certain personal details including, without limitation, Your full name, email address, postal address, telephone number, fax, profile, preferred username, etc. This information is primarily used to contact You to confirm and verify, to inform You about Your account activity, to inform You about the contest(s) that match Your profile, or any other matter that We think deserves to be informed about. Such miscellaneous matters include, without limitation, resolving disputes, providing customer support, troubleshooting, managing payments to and from the Website, and enforcing Our Terms of Service Agreement and other legal policies regarding Your use of this Website. We may also use Your email address to send newsletters, updates, and news from the Website. However, You are free to opt-out of the mailing list by managing Your account. Personal information may include your age, including whether you are 40 years or older.

Non-Personal Information: While You are accessing, browsing, and/or using this Website in any capacity – member or non-member – We also collect certain non-personal information. This information is in the form of usage statistics and includes, without limitation, Your Internet Protocol (IP) Address, Your browser-type & version, the operating system installed on Your computer, Your Internet Service Provider’s (ISP’s) IP Address, the time-stamp of Your visit, etc. This non-personal information is used to enhance Your browsing experience of this Website, improve Website and system administration, conduct internal research, compile and provide statistical data to the advertisers to deliver targeted advertisements.

Payment Information: If you use this Website to make or receive payments, we will also collect certain payment information, such as credit card, PayPal or other financial account information, and billing address.

Identity Verification: We may collect personal information, such as your date of birth or taxpayer identification number, to validate your identity or as may be required by law, such as to complete tax filings. We may request documents to verify this information, such as a copy of your government-issued identification or photo or a billing statement.

Information From Third Parties: We may also receive information about you from third parties. For example, we may receive information from you about other users of this Website. This specifically include feedback from other Website users about their experience with you. Please note that any feedback you provide via the Service or feedback provided about you is publicly viewable. We will all third party provided personal information it as set forth in this Policy.

### Your Information — How Do We Use it?

We may use personal information we collect for one or more of the following business purposes:

  * To fulfill or meet the reason for which the information is provided. For example, if you provide us with personal information in order for use to process payments for you, we will use that information to process payments for you.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
  * To provide you with email alerts and other notices concerning our products or services, or events or news, that may be of interest to you.
  * To improve our website and present its contents to you.
  * For testing, research, analysis and product development.
  * As necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our clients or others.
  * To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations.
  * As described to you when collecting your personal information.
  * To evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us is among the assets transferred.for other purposes with your consent, unless you withdraw your consent for these purposes.

### Your Information — When Do We Disclose it?

Third Party Service Providers: Your personal information may be held, transmitted to or processed on our behalf, including 'in the cloud', by our third party service providers, such as (a) cloud hosting, storage, networking and related providers, (b) payment and banking providers (eg. PayPal), (c) marketing and analytics providers, (d) our insurers or processional advisors (insofar as reasonably necessary) and/or (d) security providers.

Related Companies: We may disclose Your information to any member of our group of companies (this means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and all its subsidiaries) insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes, and as described in this Policy.

Other Disclosures and Transfers: We may also disclose Your personal information to third parties for the following purposes: (a) if reasonable necessary to allow You to use the Website, (b) provide the service or product You have requested; (c) we receive court orders, subpoenas or other requests for information by law enforcement; (d) if otherwise permitted or required by law; (e) or for other purposes with Your consent.

### Cookies, Web Beacons and Embedded Scripts — How and Why We Use Them?

In order to collect non-personal information, We use cookies, which are small text files placed on the hard drive of Your computer system. We use cookies to enhance Your use of the Website. Primarily, cookies are used to save Your session details and avoid multiple log-in during the same session. We use both persistent cookies that remain on your computer or similar device (such as to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Website) and session ID cookies, which expire at the end of your browser session. You can control the use of cookies at the browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functionality of the Website.

We and our marketing partners, affiliates, analytics, and service providers may also employ software technology known as “web beacons” or “embedded scripts” to help us keep track of Your use of the Website and to serve relevant advertising to you. Web beacons are invisible small graphics with a unique identifier embedded in webpages and emails, and which are used to track the online activity of users. An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about Your interactions with the Website, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your computer or other device and is deactivated or deleted when you disconnect from the Website.

In addition, we and our marketing partners, affiliates, analytics, and service providers may use a variety of other technologies (such as tags) that collect similar information for security and fraud detection purposes and we may use third parties to perform these services on our behalf.

### Do Not Track Signals

Your browser setting may allow you to automatically transmit a “Do Not Track” signal to websites and online services you visit. We do not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals.

### Forums and your Profile

We may offer public forums or blogs. If You participate, your comments and questions will be publicly displayed. You may choose, through such features or otherwise, to submit or post questions, comments, or other content. Please note that certain information, such as Your name and profile may be publicly displayed on the Website along with your submitted content. You may also submit a profile you’re your account containing your personal information. Anything You post to a forum or on your profile is public around the world and anyone may use it or share it with third parties. We cannot prevent the use (or misuse) of such personal data by others.

### Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our Website, in addition to other endorsements. With Your consent We may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us by clicking the “Contact Us” link on the homepage of the website and submitting a message through the webform provided.

### Spam Policy

We do not send any unsolicited commercial or non-commercial email to You or any of Your referred friends. You can further control the kind of communications You receive from Us by managing Your account. 

### Do We Share Any of Your Information with Other Users of Website?

Some details of Your personal profile including, without limitation, Your name, business name, area of expertise, etc., will be shared with other users of this Website. This feature is enabled so that the users can make an informed decision whether or not to conduct business with You. Your feedback ratings and comments by other users will also be publicly accessible. 

### Third Party Links

This Website may contain links to third party websites belonging to affiliates, partners, agents, and advertisers. We disclaim any responsibility for such links since We do not control or monitor the privacy practices of the linked websites. If You visit these linked websites and transact with them, You do so at Your own sole risk. All such use of the linked websites shall be subject to the terms and conditions and privacy policies of those websites. 

### Your Information — How Do We Secure It?

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with applicable law and industry best practices for the type of personal information collected. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. Refund Policy.

### Your Information — Disclosure Disclaimers

The Company shall not be liable for the disclosure of any of Your information so collected under any of the following circumstances:

  1. Disclosure to the government agencies in response to legal processes, like subpoena; or
  2. Any unlawful access to, and transmissions of, information from the Website; or
  3. Disclosure of personal information by You on any online and offline media including, without limitation, blogs, social networking websites, forums, message boards, etc.
  4. Disclosure of information to the successor of the Website in the event of sale of DesignContest.com

### What about Minors?

This Website is not intended for children under the age of 18 and you may not use this website or submit any data to this website if you are under the age of 18. If we find we have collected any data from anyone under the age of 18, we will delete it.

### Any Questions or Complaints? Contact Us

If You still have any questions on the privacy of Your information, feel free to contact us. We’ll respond to all the queries promptly and appropriately.

By Email:[admin@designcontest.com](mailto:admin@designcontest.com)

### For California Residents Only

Access to Specific Information.

You can request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months, including: (a) the categories and sources of personal information we collected about you, (b) Our purpose for collecting or sharing that information, (c) the categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information, including the categories if information each category of third parties received and the business reasons for sharing, and (d) The specific pieces of personal information we collected (a “data portability request”).

Deletion Request Rights.

We will delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies. We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service provider(s) to: (a) Complete the processing of your loan request or otherwise perform our contract with you, (b) detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities, (c) debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality, (d) exercise another provided for by law, (e) comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 et. seq.).

Exercising Access, Data Portability, and Deletion Rights.

To exercise the access, data portability, and deletion rights described above, please submit a verifiable consumer request to us by sending an email to [admin@designcontest.com](mailto:admin@designcontest.com) with the exact subject line “California Resident Exercising Access, Data Portability, or Deletion Rights” or by calling 888-906-1888.

Only you, or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period.

The verifiable consumer request must: (a) Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative and (b) Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.

We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you. We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor’s identity or authority to make the request.

We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable consumer request unless it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request. We will confirm receipt of your request within 10 days and will respond within 45 days – although we may take an addition 45 days (for a total of 90 days total) if proper notice and explanation for the delay is provided.

Personal Information Sales Opt-Out and Opt-In Rights

You have the right to direct us to not sell your personal information at any time by sending an email to [admin@designcontest.com](mailto:admin@designcontest.com) with the exact subject line “California Resident Personal Information Sales Opt-Out” or by calling 1-800-772-2274.

California’s “Shine the Light” law

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of this Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [admin@designcontest.com](mailto:admin@designcontest.com) with the exact subject line “California Resident Shine the Light Request” or write to us to physical address above.

Other Disclosures

All of the categories of information described in the “What Do We Do with Your Personal Information?” section above have been collected and disclosed by us in the preceding 12 months. We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your rights described in this “For California Residents Only” section or any other rights granted to you under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018. We do not collect or share any of the following information about you: signature, physical characteristics or description, passport number, medical information, health insurance information, race, color, ancestry, national origin, religion or creed, medical condition, physical or mental disability, sexual orientation, veteran status, genetic information (including familial genetic information).

### For European Union Residents Only

This Website is hosted in and operated from the United States and so all of your personal data is transferred to Us in the United States. We are the controller of your information collected on this Website.

You have the following rights with regard to your information: (a) the right to access your data; (b) the right to rectification of inaccurate data; (c) the right to erasure without undue delay; (d) the right to restrict processing; (e) the right to object to processing; (f) the right to data portability; (g) the right to complain to a supervisory authority; and (h) the right to withdraw consent.

If you wish to exercise any of these rights, email [admin@designcontest.com](mailto:admin@designcontest.com) with the subject line “Exercising European Union GDPR Rights” to make this request. Otherwise, your data may be stored indefinitely. Your data will not be transferred across borders, other than its initial transmission to the US when you submit your information to us.

Our data protection officer's contact details are:

DesignContest LLC

ATTN: Data Protection Officer 

2121 Tropicana Ave, Suite 2

Las Vegas, NV 89119

Email: [admin@designcontest.com](mailto:admin@designcontest.com)
